<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://angularcamp.org/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://angularcamp.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 21:12:12 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 21:12:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Diversity Tickets</title>
        <description>&lt;h4 id=&quot;diversity-tickets-now-accepting-applications&quot;&gt;Diversity Tickets: Now accepting applications&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have now opened &lt;a href=&quot;http://goo.gl/forms/BJErZJTpLL&quot;&gt;our application&lt;/a&gt; for our Diversity Attendee Tickets. If you would like to apply, fill out our &lt;a href=&quot;http://goo.gl/forms/BJErZJTpLL&quot;&gt;easy question application&lt;/a&gt;. These are free tickets to AngularCamp supported by generous community members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since we are a non-profit conference, it is tough to give out free tickets, but we start one of our new initiatives is to reserve a contingent of tickets for groups and organisations that work on diversity in tech and offer them to buy a ticket outside of the regular and hectic ticket release schedule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe that a more diverse crowd makes for a better event and community. If you agree, we invite you to become a Diversity Suporter by buying one of the &lt;strong&gt;five&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://ti.to/angularcamp/angularcamp-july-barcelona/with/wefcyijlk4y&quot;&gt;Diversity Supporter tickets&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 01:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://angularcamp.org/blog/diversity-tickets</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://angularcamp.org/blog/diversity-tickets</guid>
        
        
            
        
            
            <category>en</category>
            
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Speakers &amp; Schedule</title>
        <description>&lt;h4 id=&quot;news&quot;&gt;News&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;because-learning-never-exhausts-the-mind-br-join-us-to-learn-share--discover-at-angularcamp&quot;&gt;Because learning never exhausts the mind. &lt;br /&gt; Join us to Learn, Share &amp;amp; Discover at AngularCamp&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are thrilled to announce first Angular Conference happening in Barcelona @ &lt;a href=&quot;http://ajuntament.barcelona.cat/dissenyhub/en&quot;&gt;Disseny Hub Barcelona&lt;/a&gt; and also we &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/groups/angularcamp/pool&quot;&gt;repeat experience&lt;/a&gt; with AngularCamp: a multi track un-conference style with more than 25 contributors a day by people inside the community like you and a lot of activities to engage people to start: learning, sharing, discovering all together in a safe environment for everybody. You decide what will happen: &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/AngularCamp/angularcamp.org/issues/new&quot;&gt;send us your interest or your contribution&lt;/a&gt; (a talk? a workshop? do you have a crazy idea? &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/AngularCamp/angularcamp.org/issues/new&quot;&gt;we want to hear you&lt;/a&gt; ^__^&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We want to keep motivation, illusion and passion inside Angular community providing to our members a more affordable ticket prices just for covering event expenses: this includes creating an atmosphere where everyone feels welcome as well as different activities with  best selected venues that fits with your needs to make it happen!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AngularCamp Conference is a non-profit and single track conference carefully crafted with love for you with twelve talks a day by internationally renowned community speakers, hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;community-speakers&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;Community Speakers&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Uri Shaked.  BlackBerry, Israel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Todd Motto. Telerik, U.K.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Thorsten Hans. Thinktecture, Germany
&lt;!-- * PatrickJS. AngularClass, U.S. --&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Evan Schultz.  rangle.io, Canada&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wassim Chegman. SFEIR, France&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Maxim Salnikov. ForgeRock, Norway&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Manfred Steyer. SoftwareArchitekt.at, Austria&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Uri Goldshtein.  Meteor, Israel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sebastian Witalek.  Telerik, UK&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vanesa Yuen. rangle.io, Canada&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Igor Kamenetsky. rangle.io, Canada&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Christoffer Noring.  Ovo Energy, Sweden&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;organizers&quot;&gt;&amp;gt; Organizers&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AngularCamp is organized by &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/davidpichcanes&quot;&gt;David Pich&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.meetup.com/AngularJS-Beers/&quot;&gt;AngularBeers&lt;/a&gt;, the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ub.edu/minerva/ciencies-socials-i-humanitats&quot;&gt;University of Barcelona&lt;/a&gt; and co-organized with our friend &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/jowe&quot;&gt;Johannes Weber&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.meetup.com/AngularJS-Munich/&quot;&gt;AngularJS Munich&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;check-out-the-schedule&quot;&gt;&amp;gt; Check out the schedule&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Still subject to change, so please check often)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://angularcamp.org/schedule/&quot;&gt;http://angularcamp.org/schedule/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;rsvp-your-ticket-now-limited-tickets&quot;&gt;&amp;gt; RSVP your ticket now: [limited tickets]&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://angularcamp.org/tickets/&quot;&gt;http://angularcamp.org/tickets/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;ticket-includes-&quot;&gt;&amp;gt; Ticket includes :&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Food, drinks, fun and some surprises we will announce soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More details about workshops will appear in subsequent posts, meantime like us on &lt;a href=&quot;https://facebook.com/AngularCamp&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, follow on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/intent/user?screen_name=AngularCamp&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, add to circles in &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.google.com/b/109504483341774220838/?pageId=109504483341774220838&quot;&gt;Google+&lt;/a&gt; or subcribe to our &lt;a href=&quot;https://angularcamp.us13.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=d2fc5475a20b56ece3dfa9263&amp;amp;id=9ffe132f5e&quot;&gt;mailing list&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://angularcamp.org/feed.xml&quot;&gt;RSS feed&lt;/a&gt; in order not to miss any cool stuff about AngularCamp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 02:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://angularcamp.org/blog/angularcamp-schedule-speakers</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://angularcamp.org/blog/angularcamp-schedule-speakers</guid>
        
        
            
        
            
            <category>en</category>
            
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello World!</title>
        <description>&lt;h4 id=&quot;welcome-to-your-community&quot;&gt;Welcome to your community&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First AngularCamp has been an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/groups/angularcamp/pool&quot;&gt;unbelievable community experience&lt;/a&gt; and we are excited to announce the first Angular Camp &amp;amp; Conference in Barcelona @ &lt;a href=&quot;http://ajuntament.barcelona.cat/dissenyhub/en&quot;&gt;Disseny Hub Barcelona&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tickets will be limited so get notified when tickets are available by &lt;a href=&quot;http://angularcamp.us13.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=d2fc5475a20b56ece3dfa9263&amp;amp;id=9ffe132f5e&quot;&gt;signing up to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; and don’t miss out the opportunity of joining a growing community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;event-quick-facts&quot;&gt;Event quick facts&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So should you also be excited? Well yes… and here’s why!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Attendance&lt;/strong&gt;: we’re expecting over 320 attendees&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Topic&lt;/strong&gt;: more than 30 hours of Angular topics related&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date&lt;/strong&gt;: 1-2-3 July, expect workshops on 30th June, Angular Conference on the 1st July and camp 2nd-3rd July.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Venue&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&quot;http://ajuntament.barcelona.cat/dissenyhub/en&quot;&gt;Disseny Hub Barcelona&lt;/a&gt; - with an amazing cinema screen 16:9&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speakers&lt;/strong&gt;: we’re in the process of getting proposals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;but we’ve already secured a first batch of experts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Todd Motto&lt;/strong&gt; - Todd is a Developer Advocate at Telerik. Google Developer Expert&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wassim Chegham&lt;/strong&gt; - Core contributor to Angular Universal and more. JavaScript enthusiast • Angular GDE.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Uri Shaked&lt;/strong&gt; - Google Developer Expert for AngularJS. He created the popular angular-moment open source module and regularly speaks about Web-related technologies in conferences and meetups. Among his interests are reverse engineering, hardware hacking, playing music and Salsa dancing. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More details about speakers, workshops will appear in subsequent posts, meantime like us on &lt;a href=&quot;https://facebook.com/AngularCamp&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, follow on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/intent/user?screen_name=AngularCamp&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, add to circles in &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.google.com/b/109504483341774220838/?pageId=109504483341774220838&quot;&gt;Google+&lt;/a&gt; or subcribe to our &lt;a href=&quot;https://angularcamp.us13.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=d2fc5475a20b56ece3dfa9263&amp;amp;id=9ffe132f5e&quot;&gt;mailing list&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://angularcamp.org/feed.xml&quot;&gt;RSS feed&lt;/a&gt; in order not to miss any cool stuff about AngularCamp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;focused-on-the-attendees&quot;&gt;Focused on the attendees&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An AngularCamp can’t get compared with annual worldwide AngularJS conferences: AngularCamp wants to keep motivation and passion inside community with more constant meetups driven from inside the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AngularCamps don’t need to be big, fancy or expensive events. AngularCamps are meant to be focused on the attendees and their expectations  in a cost effective way, based on the local investment available to support it. Typically venues should be cheap to allow attendees to join the event and make it more accessible to all in order to attend, meet people, share experiences and knowledge, and learn together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supporters and donations make all this possible, keeping ticket prices very low below for a 2-day event. It’s not strange that also collaborators will join for free because all it’s focused to create a sustainable community as well a safe environment where everyone can join the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;engage-collaboration&quot;&gt;Engage collaboration.&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We want to use the internet to get off the internet. Getting to meet and learn from other people face-to-face is one of the main reasons people attend AngularCamps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to AngularCamps’ volunteers, they  will try to help fellow attendees with their questions in addition to learning from each other. Attendees have a great opportunity to find new friends, collaborators and potential inspiration in the AngularCamp crowd. All these can lead to an exciting, sustainable and engaged community driven.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every AngularCamp is a “big event” of a local AngularJS meetup group (indeed if it doesn’t exist is a great way to kick it off)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;think-globally-act-locally&quot;&gt;Think globally, act locally&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AngularCamp calendar is coordinated by AngularCamp.org but each individual meetup is organized by local AngularJS people. We will provide guidance but we not taking any decisions. AngularCamp are not meant to be an event with the same collaborators at every event, so we will try to tend to have both local and visiting collaborators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;supporters&quot;&gt;Supporters&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to get involved and help support AngularCamp Barcelona?&lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#108;&amp;#108;&amp;#111;&amp;#064;&amp;#097;&amp;#110;&amp;#103;&amp;#117;&amp;#108;&amp;#097;&amp;#114;&amp;#099;&amp;#097;&amp;#109;&amp;#112;&amp;#046;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#103;&quot;&gt;We’d love to hear from you&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;non-profit&quot;&gt;Non-profit&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AngularCamps will use supporters money and donations to benefit the community not treated as profit to be pocketed by the organizers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AngularCamps organized as money-making opportunities are not approved to use the AngularCamp name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;safe-environment--fun&quot;&gt;Safe environment &amp;amp; Fun&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AngularCamps are meant to be focused on: safe environment (CoC), learning, sharing and socialize with people but most important: have fun without lose the focus. There will be different activities, spaces and actions to make it happen (need to go beyond the code)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 01:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://angularcamp.org/blog/hello-world</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://angularcamp.org/blog/hello-world</guid>
        
        
            
        
            
            <category>en</category>
            
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Call for Papers</title>
        <description>&lt;h4 id=&quot;angularcamp-barcelona-2016&quot;&gt;AngularCamp Barcelona 2016&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may be wondering what’s going on in an AngularCamp. The first AngularCamp happened in &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.meetup.com/AngularCamp/events/227759458/&quot;&gt;30-31th January 2016&lt;/a&gt; and we hope the next ones will come easily to more locations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AngularCamp Barcelona 2016 will be held 1st-2nd-3rd of July. If you want to be part of this growing community event as a speaker contact &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#097;&amp;#110;&amp;#103;&amp;#117;&amp;#108;&amp;#097;&amp;#114;&amp;#099;&amp;#097;&amp;#109;&amp;#112;&amp;#046;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#103;&quot;&gt;hello@angularcamp.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone from newbies to experts are welcome to participate in order to share, learn and get to know each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Angular Camp Barcelona is proudly organized by &lt;a href=&quot;http://angularbeers.org&quot;&gt;Angular &amp;amp; Beers&lt;/a&gt; in collaboration with the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ub.edu/minerva/ciencies-socials-i-humanitats&quot;&gt;University of Barcelona&lt;/a&gt; @ Park Humanities and Social Sciences&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;angularcamp-conference-1st-july-themes-and-topics&quot;&gt;AngularCamp Conference (1st July): themes and topics&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team prepared set of interesting topics in but if you have any cool idea you want to share, feel free to submit it as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;angular-camp-2nd-3rd-july&quot;&gt;Angular Camp (2nd-3rd July):&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone is invited to give a talk: at the days of the conference we all vote together which talks we would love to see - the talks with the most votes will be put on the schedule then.
We are looking forward to many awesome sessions with you at AngularCamp!
You can propose them by adding a new issue on https://github.com/AngularCamp/angularcamp.org/issues&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;please-submit-your-proposals-herehttpgooglformsuy5tobgzcp&quot;&gt;Please submit your proposals &lt;a href=&quot;http://goo.gl/forms/UY5toBgzcP&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline&lt;/strong&gt; is May 1, 2016&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note:&lt;/strong&gt; There is no guarantee that a submission will be put onto the conference agenda!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The program committee picks the most interesting talk proposals and informs the selected submitters until May 15, 2016.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;any-questions&quot;&gt;Any questions?&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email organizers at &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#097;&amp;#110;&amp;#103;&amp;#117;&amp;#108;&amp;#097;&amp;#114;&amp;#099;&amp;#097;&amp;#109;&amp;#112;&amp;#046;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#103;&quot;&gt;hello@angularcamp.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 02:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://angularcamp.org/blog/call-for-papers</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://angularcamp.org/blog/call-for-papers</guid>
        
        
            
        
            
            <category>en</category>
            
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
